早上好 总统女士
Good morning, Madam President.
请允许我向您介绍爪洼国大使
May I introduce you to the Ambassador of Java?
多谢
Oh, thank you.
因为追根究底 旅行水杯
Because, after all, what is a travel mug
就是你装咖啡的橱柜
but a closet for your coffee?
很好 这就是我们下一轮营销方式了
And boom, our next promotional giveaway.
你要是穿上高领毛衣和牛仔裤
Throw on a black turtleneck and some mom jeans,
我会感觉自己娶了史蒂夫·乔布斯
it's like I'm married to Steve Jobs.
我听到你昨晚发邮件
I did hear you banging out e-mails
发到了很晚
till all hours last night,
所以三明治里的黄瓜片还能用来
so the cucumbers in the sandwich can be repurposed
在午休时间消除鱼尾纹
as lunchtime crow's-feet refreshers.
谢谢
Thank you.
别忘了晚点有个酒会
Don't forget we've got drinks later.
好 有没有什么玩笑不能开的
Right. Any specific joke areas I should stay away from?
没有 不用担心
Oh, no, don't worry about it.
主要是我和其他人聊工作
It's mostly just me and the guys talking business.
我给你报的单车健身课你去上了吗
Hey, you using those spin classes I got you?
我上周去了两次呢
Yeah. I went twice last week.
看不出来吗
You can't tell?
当然能
Sure, I can.
接手老爸公司最棒的一点在于
The best part about taking over my dad's company --
我成了一个大权在握的白人男性 我爱这感觉
I am now a powerful white male, and I love it.
我现在完全能体会为什么我们不希望
I totally get now why we don't want anyone else
其他族群拥有我们拥有的这一切
to have what we have.
亲爱的 在我去上班之前
Honey, before I take off for work,
我看到了这个 然后想到了你
I saw this and I thought of you.
这是什么
What is it?
是一把钥匙
It's a key?
没错
Yeah, it is.
是一把钥匙
It is a key...
但这是什么的钥匙呢
but a key to what?
不是吧
No!
你给我买了个平衡车
You got me a PhunkeeDuck?!
我的男人不再需要走路了 笨蛋才走路
No more walking for my man. Walking's for jerks.
天哪 有史以来最棒的礼物
Oh, my God! That is the best gift ever!
管它会去到哪里 我出发了
I don't know where it stops and I begin!
在哪里 在哪里
Where is it? Where is it?
这些奶酪块一周比一周小了
You know, these cheese cubes keep getting smaller every week.
我得开始保留样本证明这一点了
I should start saving these to prove my point.
退休以后居然闲到这种程度
Wow, am I retired.
在那里
It's there!
太美了
It's beautiful!
穿得有点暴露了
A little revealing.
我能理解利用性感来制造辣酱的卖点
I mean, I get using sex to sell your hot sauce.
这也是为何我以前拍橱柜广告要穿约达西牛仔裤
That's why I wore Jordache jeans in my old closet ads.
这也有点太过了吧
But a little much, isn't it?
效果显然很好
It's obviously working.
店里跟我说他们摆出来一百瓶酱
The store said that they put out
现在已经卖掉一半了
100 bottles of my sauce, and half of them are gone!
天哪
Oh, my.
爱丽丝姑姑
Auntie Alice!
她是辣酱业的传说
She's a hot-sauce legend.
她家的丙级辣酱
Her Level Three Sauce
宣传画是一只爆炸的公鸡
has a picture of a rooster exploding.
我得去见见她
I have to go meet her.
快过来 照张相
Hey, guys, take a pic.
滚一边去 这是我的老婆
Hey, get out of here! That's my wife!
我是你的超级粉丝
I am a huge fan.
您瓶罐上的人生故事我读了超多遍
I have read your life story on your label a thousand times.
您父亲真的开着装辣椒的卡车
Is it true that your father crashed his pepper truck
撞上了木瓜树 因此开启了一代传奇吗
into a papaya tree and the legend was born?
你还问我什么事是真的吗
You're asking me if something's real?
我不敢相信那块人形板真的是个人
I can't believe that that cutout's an actual person.
迈尔斯
Miles?
你好 杰
Oh, hey, Jay.
我想看看这条短信
Uh, trying to read a text.
这边灯光被调得很暗
They keep the lights in here so low
这样就不用把旧货撤下来了
so they don't have to rotate the produce.
少扯了
Don't give me that.
不好意思
I'm sorry, man.
雷妮塔离开以后我一直很寂寞
I've been lonely since Reynetta left.
去你的
You're a deacon.
亲爱的 帮我按按脚
Honey, foot rub.
不要
Pass.
好吧 又来了
Okay, there it is again!
我告诉你 楼上肯定在搞什么奇怪的事
I'm telling you, something weird is going on up there.
我们把楼上的房间出租好赚点外快
We're renting our upstairs unit to earn a little extra cash
也给我们的婚姻添一丝紧张感
and add a little extra tension to our marriage.
现在的租客自称是
Our current guests registered
威尔克森夫妇及汤米
as Mr. And Mrs. Wilkerson and Tommy.
我以为是一对带小男孩的年轻夫妇
I was expecting a nice young couple and their little boy.
你好 你们
Hello. You --
你们肯定就是威尔克森夫妇了吧
So, you -- You must be Mr. And Mrs. Wilkerson?
-没错 -那你就是汤米了
- That's right. - So you're Tommy?
正是
He is.
欢迎
Welcome.
小卡 我们去帮他们搬东西
Cam, let's help them with their trunk.
不用
No!
不用吗 好吧 这是钥匙
No? Okay, well, uh, here is the key.
-给 -谢谢
- Here you are. - Thank you.
汤米
Tommy?
这算怎么回事
Okay, what is that all about?
三个成年人
I mean, three adults?
汤米为什么没有姓
Why doesn't Tommy have a last name?
汤米为什么不说话 他是人质吗
Why doesn't Tommy talk? Is he their captive?
还是说人质其实是威尔克森太太
Is Mrs. Wilkerson their captive?
还是说人质其实在车的后备箱
Is the captive in the trunk?
所以一定要有人质吗
So there has to be a captive?
最近 有些租客给了我们
Lately, we've been getting negative reviews
-负面评价 -直说吧
- from some of our renters. - Say it.
他们都提到一个共同的问题
And they tend to follow the common theme
"大个子"喜欢八卦
that the "Bigger one" is "Nosy".
而其他人说"橙发的家伙"
While others say the "Orange fella"
很冷漠不友好
is "Standoffish and cold."
谁说的
Who says that?
我刚说的
I'm saying it now.
好吧 我们得弄清楚到底怎么一回事
Okay, we need to find out what that is.
小卡 不要去管他们好吗
Cam, stay out of their business, all right?
要是我们的评价掉到三颗星以下
If we drop below three stars,
就只能租给烟鬼
we're gonna be stuck renting to chain smokers
或者想来美国生小孩的外国孕妇了
and pregnant foreigners trying to have their babies in America.
记好时间 我开始变身成我爸了
Mark down the time. I just turned into my father.
我要上去
I'm going up.
小卡
Cam...
小卡 你在干什么
Cam, what are you doing?!
我去看看我们的租客
I am checking on our guests.
你们好 三位都好
Hello! Oh, all three of you.
我就是过来看看你们是不是需要
Uh, just stopped by to see if you guys need
一些干净的 干净的毛巾
some fresh -- fresh towels.
我们不需要 谢谢
We're fine, thank you.
你是有什么话要说吗
Uh, yes, you were gonna say something?
你也看到了对吧
You saw that, right?
威尔克森太太朝我做了个痛苦的表情
Mrs. Wilkerson was giving me the distress signal.
她刚刚这样...
She was like...
拜托
Come on.
小卡
Cam!
又是我们 就是想再来看看
Us again. Just triple-checking
你们是不是需要肥皂
to see if you need some hand soap,
单独跟我俩其中一个讲话 或者蛋糕
a chance to talk to one of us alone, some muffins.
我们真的不需要 你不用一直过来问
Really, we're fine. You don't have to keep checking.
阿嚏[救命]
Help!
她说的不是救命
She did not say "Help."
看来你听到了
So you did hear it.
胖子 替我谢谢你妈给我弄的新壁纸
Hey, Delgado, thank your mom for my new screen saver.
我会的 帕克
Will do, Parker.
说到二维纸板做的女人
And speaking of two-dimensional women
刚好对酱料又略懂一二
who know a thing or two about sauce,
你路过弗拉纳根酒吧时也替我问你妈好
stop by Flanagan's and say hi to your mom for me.
我知道你是因为那个人形板不开心
I know you were bothered by that cutout.
但是所有青少年都有被嘲笑的时候
But every teenager gets teased,
你得克服这种感觉 这样
and you have to rise above it, so --
-你妈在后备箱里 -什么
- Your mother's in the trunk. - What?
我受不了那些垂涎的眼神还有猥琐的自拍
I couldn't stand the ogling and the selfies,
所以我 为了我们俩把那人形板偷出来了
so I stole it -- for both our sakes.
我们俩是一伙儿的
We're in this together.
怎么会 我可没偷它出来
How? I didn't steal it.
我知道这是怎么回事了
Oh, I see where this is going.
你抱怨个没完 然后我把问题解决了
You complain and complain, I make the problem go away,
你就过河拆桥
and you had nothing to do with it.
我又没让你这么做 都是你自己的想法
I didn't ask for this. I didn't ask for any of this.
别起内讧了 会让我们掉以轻心的
Let's not turn on each other. It'll make us sloppy.
我需要你帮忙处理掉它
I need your help to get rid of it.
我已经努力尝试过了
God knows I've already tried.
我了个
Son of a...
亚洲新推了很多很棒的收纳方案 是吧
A lot of cool storage solutions coming out of Asia, huh?
是的 的确是
Yeah, there really are.
但是我觉得你会对
But I think you might be even more interested
古巴生产的好东西更感兴趣
in what's been coming out of Cuba.
她难道不是最棒的吗
Is she the best or what?
我们出去来一根吧
Shall we, hmm?
走起
Let's do it.
亲爱的 我们只是去谈工作的
You know what, honey? We are just gonna talk about work.
要不你留下再喝一杯
Why don't you stay and have another drink, huh?
你不用扭我胳膊的
Well, you don't have to twist my arm.
女士们如何 再喝一轮蓝宝石之罪[鸡尾酒]
What do you say, ladies? Another round of Sapphire Sins?
好的呀
Ooh, yes, please.
菲尔 你太风趣了
Phil, you are just so much fun.
谢谢
Thank you.
从男人嘴里听到这句话
Oh, it is so nice to hear those words
真是太好了
come out of a man's mouth.
不就是嘛
Tell me about it.
自从凯尔升了职
Ever since Kyle got that promotion,
他就不怎么理我了
he barely acknowledges me.
拜托 他肯定知道自己有多幸运
Come on, now, I'm sure he knows how lucky he is.
你生了双胞胎 把房子打理得一尘不染
You have the twins, a spotless house,
还拥有线条完美的手臂
killer yoga arms.
总是这样的
This happens all the time --
他们走在通向成功的路上
They get on their track to success,
我们就成了不被重视的家庭主妇
and you become the invisible housewife.
我可不常有这种感觉
I don't know about all the time.
跟那群女人坐在一起时 我在想
Sitting with all those gals, I thought,
"哇 这香水味儿可真浓得呛人"
"Wow, this is an insane amount of perfume."
"还有 我是不是也逐渐"
"And also, am I on my way"
"变成一个不被重视的家庭主妇"
"to becoming an invisible housewife?"
不可能 起码也会有征兆不是吗
No way. There'd be signs, right?
回来啦 一直给你留着热菜呢
Hey, stranger. Been keeping dinner warm for ya.
真好 不过我在俱乐部吃过牛排了
Oh, that's nice. I had a steak at the club.
不过我想喝你手里那杯苏格兰威士忌
But I wouldn't knock a Scotch out of your hands.
没问题
Sure thing.
现在是不是可以
Hey, is now an okay time
过一遍这张家务清单
to go over this list of house stuff?
看看呗
Let's see.
随意 随意 找人解决 随意
Don't care, don't care, call a guy, don't care.
猜猜是谁今天搞定西山社区的大单子了
Guess who got the big listing on Westmount today.
太棒了 宝贝 工作能让你有点事干
Oh, that's great, sweetie. It'll keep you busy.
那是只新手镯吗
Is that a new bracelet?
是的
Oh, yes, it is.
吉姆上次和我大吵了之后买给我的
Jim bought it for me after our last big fight.
我怪他老是出差
I was on him about taking all those business trips.
他们就这样
That's what they do.
给你买新的珠宝首饰来哄你开心
Throw some new piece of jewelry at you to keep you happy.
没错 倒也没什么可抱怨的
Mm-hmm. Not that I'm complaining.
没错吧
Right?
太好了 老妈的车不在
Oh, good, Mom's car is gone.
好 我的手锯在车库里
All right. My handsaw is in the garage.
你按住立模 我来把头锯掉
You'll hold her down, I'll cut the head off.
杰
Jay!
我的车爆胎然后被拖走了
My car got a flat tire, so it got towed.
我得搭你的车去菲尔家
I need a ride to Phil's.
他在帮我搞定我的酱料网站
He's helping me finish my sauce website.
曼尼 宝贝 你哭什么呢
Manny, baby, why are you crying?
我没哭
I'm not.
商场又给我发邮件了
Ooh, I got another e-mail from the store.
准是我又卖了
I bet you that I sold another --
搞什么鬼 有人偷了我的人形板
What the hell? Somebody stole my cutout.
被人偷了 气死我也
Stolen? Damn it!
重新换一个也没意义
Well, there's no point in replacing it
反正换好了又要被偷
because it's just gonna get stolen again.
换不了了
I can't replace it.
光是让机械臂正常动起来
It took two weeks
就已经花了两个星期
just to get the mechanical arm working right.
等着我抓到这个小贼吧
Oh, wait till I catch this rat.
我一定会让他后悔偷了我的
I'm going to make him regret that he was ever...
杰 开开暖气吧
Hey, Jay, turn the heater on.
我都能听到曼尼的牙齿在打颤
I can hear Manny's teeth chattering.
什么声音
What is that noise?
我没听到有声音
I don't hear anything.
怎么这么大声
What is that thumping noise?
曼尼 到车尾箱看看
Manny, go check the trunk.
我不想弄脏手[蹚浑水] 杰
Uh, I don't really feel like getting my hands dirty, Jay.
你的手已经很脏了 哥们儿
Your hands are plenty dirty already, buddy boy.
快去看看[搞定]吧
Go deal with it.
我一定要找出是谁干的 杰
I am going to find who did this, Jay,
我会让他生不如死
and I'm going to make him hurt.
所有窃贼都会出纰漏
Every thief makes a mistake.
歌洛莉亚 你让这事影响到你心情了
Gloria, you're letting this get to you.
你知道什么能让你冷静下来吗
You know what always calms you down?
乔爱听的小鸭之歌
Joe's little duck song.
现在我们 我们来听吧
Now, let's -- Let's get that going.
我恨他
I hate him.
*呱呱呱 加入小鸭游行队*
*Quack, quack, quack, join the duck parade*
我要让他见血
I want blood!
*摇摇摆摆 摇摇摆摆 不停地走*
*Waddle, waddle, waddle, waddle, watch them wade*
*翘起尾巴 低下脑袋*
*Tail up, head down*
*甩甩羽毛扭扭腰*
*Shake your feathers all around*
*大家都来开心地看小鸭游行队*
*Everybody's smiling at the duck parade*
商场就发了个这么模糊的监控视频
This grainy security footage is all the store sent?
我觉得我认识他 菲尔
I feel like I know him, Phil.
不管他是谁 看着好像成心想被抓
Whoever it is, it looks like they want to get caught.
他不停地回去拿奶酪块
He keeps going back for the cheese cubes.
我不想再看了
I can't watch this anymore.
-我们来弄我的网站 好吗 -好呀
- Let's just work on my website, okay? - Sure.
菲尔 我约了客户要迟到了
Phil, I'm late for an appointment with a client.
你能帮我个忙吗
Can you do me a favor?
如果是把花放进浴室 我已经放好了
If it's to put flowers in the bathroom, I already did.
我没注意到
Oh, I hadn't noticed.
你注意到才怪
Not surprised.
我本来该给这位客户带一瓶苏格兰威士忌
Okay, I was supposed to get this client a bottle of Scotch.
可我一直没时间亲自去拿给他
I haven't had time to do it myself.
你能拿一瓶送到我办公室去吗
So can you pick one up and bring it down to the office?
没问题
Whatever you need.
我反正要出门理个发
I have to go out for a haircut anyway.
太好了
Great.
只不过我昨天已经理过发了
Except I got a haircut yesterday.
好 厨房真乱 对吧
Okay, wow. This kitchen really is a mess, huh?
我走了
I'm off.
别拍我屁股
Don't.
抱歉 歌洛莉亚
Excuse me, Gloria.
很明显我不懂该怎么保持厨房整洁
Apparently, I don't know how to keep a kitchen clean.
那是什么
What is that?
这是个小小的封口礼物
Oh, it's just a little hush-up gift
好让大权在握的妻子对我感到心安理得
from my powerful wife who thinks she can take me for granted.
然后我就继续像个小狗狗一样围着她转
And I'll just hover after her like a little puppy dog.
你不能再这么忍着了
You have to stop putting up with it.
他们不是故意的 但这种忽视只会愈演愈烈
They don't mean to ignore you, but it will only get worse.
我刚嫁给杰那时候
One time when I had just married Jay,
曾花一整天时间做他最爱吃的晚餐
I spent a whole day cooking his favorite dinner.
威灵顿牛排和带配料的焗土豆吗
Beef Wellington and a baked potato with all the fixin's?
是的
Yes.
但他回家后 根本没注意我做了什么
And then when he got home, he barely noticed what I have made.
于是我就把他送我的绿宝石项链坠拿出来
So I took the emerald pendant that he had bought me
他送我那个是因为错过了之前的三顿晚饭
for the three past dinners that he had missed
我把吊坠扔他头上
and I threw it at his head.
告诉他我不需要这些漂亮珠宝
I told him I don't need fancy things.
我需要尊重
I need the respect.
你脖子上是个绿宝石吊坠吗
Isn't that an emerald pendant?
后来它又回到了我手里
It made its way back to me.
但重点在于你得表达你的意见
But the point is that you have to make a statement.
你得把那个平衡板还回去
You have to give back the hoverboard.
虽然我不想承认 但你说的对
You know what? I hate to admit it, but you're right.
菲尔
Phil?
有时会这样
This happens.
只要等电池耗尽就好了
You just got to let the battery run out.
邮票用完了 我要去趟邮局
We're out of stamps. I'm heading to the post office.
要带点什么吗
Do you need anything?
不用了
No, I'm good.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
只是研究点东西
Oh, uh, just a little research.
《威尔克森和成年汤米以及神秘行李箱》
"Wilkersons plus adults Tommy plus mysterious trunk."
不如试着搜搜
Okay, now try Googling
《荒谬的闲人以及同性恋》
"Irrational meddling plus homosexual."
米奇尔 万一他们来自什么奇怪的邪教呢
Okay, Mitchell, what if they're a part of some weird cult?
记得我们看的那个片子吗
Remember that "20/20" we watched
他们在里面潜入那个宗教仪式
where they infiltrated the ritual ceremony
伊丽莎白·瓦尔加斯差点被迫拿一只松鼠献祭
and Elizabeth Vargas had to almost sacrifice a squirrel?
我检查了他们扔在垃圾桶里的袋子
I went through the bag they dumped in the trash.
你还把咱闺女牵扯进来了
Now you're involving our daughter?
我不知道她在说啥
I don't know what she's talking about.
好吧 你得离开这间屋子
Okay, you know what? You need to get out of the house.
你去买邮票
Go get the stamps.
再找个新爱好
And a hobby.
他们在我们家里
Okay, well, they're in our home,
我只是在保护我们的家
and I'm just trying to protect our family.
我可不想哪天醒来发现自己死了
I don't want to wake up dead.
真不敢相信我得再跟你说一遍
I can't believe I have to say this to you again.
死人怎么会醒过来
You cannot wake up and be dead.
我就那么一说
It's an expression!
才不是
It's not.
大爸不该让你跟他一起窥探别人
Daddy should not have involved you in his snooping.
那你不想让我告诉你我找到什么了吗
So you don't want me to tell you what I found in here?
不想
No...
我当然都查看过了
Well, of course I looked.
我在袋子里发现了乳胶手套 一瓶漂白剂
And inside I found latex gloves, a bottle of bleach,
高强度防水布
heavy-duty tarp.
我从来没有杀人然后毁尸灭迹的经验
Now, I've never killed anyone and cleaned it up,
但那包东西好像就是干这个的
but that sounds like a kit.
所以我看到他们开着那辆没窗户的
So as soon as I saw them drive off
杀人必备面包车离开时 我立刻跑上楼
in their windowless murder van, I-I ran upstairs.
我的天
Oh, my God!
这是什么
What are you?
那些人回来了
The people are back!
每天都要来这么一出吗 汤米
Is this gonna be a daily thing now, Tommy,
又忘拿手机
losing your phone?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
等等 你去哪
Wait. Where are you going?
啥事儿 我还在买邮票呢
Um, what's up? I'm still getting stamps.
看你左边
Look to your left.
你在那干啥
What are you doing?
我在隐蔽自己 他们在屋里
I'm hiding. They're here.
我上来是想看看有没有什么诡异的事发生
I came up to see if anything weird was going on.
是吗 你也好奇了 有点想管闲事吗
Did ya? Were you curious? Gettin' a little nosy?
现在不是时候
Not the time.
这些诡异的东西是啥
What are these creepy things?
如果这些玩偶会说话
If these dolls could talk...
他们会揭发我碰掉了一个而且头还摔掉了
They'd tell you I dropped one and then their head came off.
你得把它放回去
Well, you have to put it back.
说不定他们不会注意到丢了一个
Maybe they won't notice one of them's missing.
没错 这真像个正常的兴趣爱好
Yeah, this seems like a casual interest.
我的天 他们来了
Oh my gosh, here they come.
我来分散他们的注意好让你溜回去
Okay, I'll create a distraction so you can get back in there.
我只是邀请他们来享受一会儿鸡尾酒
I simply invited them to a complimentary cocktail hour.
就算可能是撒旦崇拜者也喜欢三层奶油乳酪
Even possible Satanists enjoy a triple-cream Brie
配清爽的霞多丽酒
and a crisp Chardonnay.
什么风把你们吹到这个镇上的
So, what brings you all to town?
我们是来参加微笑密友大会的
We're here for the Chuckled Chums Convention.
抱歉我没听懂 微 微笑密友是啥
I'm sorry, the -- the Chuckled Chums?
它们是一类陶瓷塑像
They're a line of ceramic figurines.
我们是狂热的收藏者
We're avid collectors.
好像很有趣
Well, that sounds fun.
是的
Yeah.
我们每年都和志同道合的密友爱好者聚在一起
Every year we gather together with like-minded Chum lovers
相互欣赏最爱的藏品
to share our favorite pieces.
什么 你 你是想说
Yes? You -- You want to say s--
阿嚏[救命]
Help!
愿你健康 亲爱的
Oh, bless you, darling.
你们可能猜到了 我是个塑像修复师
You've probably guessed. I'm the figurine restorer.
我们好激动
We're so excited.
我们的藏品是今年大会的重头戏
Ours is this year's featured collection
因为它的型号和完好的品相
because of its size and pristine condition.
我希望我们的工业抛光机没有太吵到你们
I hope the industrial polisher we brought wasn't too loud.
没有 我们根本听不见楼上有任何声音
No, we can't hear anything that goes on upstairs.
好的
Okay.
这就行了
All right.
不
Oh, no.
不 不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no!
不 不 不 不
No, no! No, no, no!
天啊 不要
Oh, God, no!
幸好 要重新集一套
Fortunately, Chuckle Chums
微笑密友并不是那么贵
aren't all that expensive to replace.
它们主要是那些孤独的人们
They're mainly just an excuse
出来结交朋友的一个由头
for lonely people to go outside.
关键是我们吸取了教训 再也不窥私了
Point is, we learned our lesson. No more snooping.
完全正确
Absolutely.
不过我们依然解释不了
Although we still don't have an explanation
那些半夜咯吱作响的地板是怎么回事
for those creaky floorboards in the middle of the night.
脚步沉重的出去 轻盈的回来
Heavy-footed going one way, light coming back.
难道汤米加入他们是为了构建三人家庭
Was it Tommy joining his chums for a menage a trois,
然后每晚和威尔克森夫人交换床位
then being replaced by Mrs. Wilkerson on the couch?
好吧 你需要 帮助
Okay, you need... help!
该死的
Son of a bitch.
这玩意一上午了废了我两把剪刀
I broke two saw blades on this thing,
现在这把神剪也快完蛋了
and now these miracle shears are no good.
在门口卖给我剪刀那家伙
Guy who sold me these at the front door
用它剪开了马蹄铁
cut through a horseshoe.
坚持住 我们来试试碎纸机
Hold on. Let's try your shredder.
这东西怎么会在这儿
What's that doing down here anyway?
我对乔的一些不重要的美术作品
I made an executive decision
做出了一项处理决定
about some of Joe's lesser artwork.
帮我把它抬起来
Help me lift this thing.
这个管用
Hey, it's working!
这是市面上能用钱买到最好的碎纸机
The best shredder money can buy.
2004年 我们机密的阻滞技术文件
In 2004, our whisper-close hamper technology
被人从垃圾桶里翻出来 放到黑市上卖了
got stolen out of the trash, got sold on the dark web.
绝不能再次发生
Never again.
不 卡住了
Oh, no, it's stuck!
我回来了
Hola!
你这么早就回来了
Hey, you're back early, huh?
是啊 我不想回到商店里触景生情
Yeah, I didn't want to go back to that store
再为那件事生气
and get angry again.
我只想好好放松下
I just want to relax.
也是
Yeah.
曼尼
Manny!
怎么了 妈妈
Uh, yes, Mama?
你能帮我准备下洗澡水
Can you please draw me a bath
放点你的浴盐进去吗
with those fancy bath salts that you have?
那些高级浴盐是留给特殊场合
Oh, I usually save those for spec--
赶紧去准备洗澡水
Just draw the damn bath.
我帮你倒杯好酒你边泡边喝吧
I'll get you a nice glass of wine to go with it.
-好啊 -开心点 亲爱的
- Oh, okay. - Come on, honey,
我这有瓶白葡萄酒你肯定会喜欢
I got a nice Chardonnay out here you're gonna like.
斯黛拉在门外吗
Is that Stella?
肯定不是
No, definitely not.
你给我带什么来啦
What did you bring?
歌洛莉亚 等等
Gloria, wait.
歌洛莉亚 先别生气
Gloria, don't be mad.
肯定是爱丽丝姑姑那个老妖婆
It must have been that old witch, Auntie Alice!
她肯定是想先用这个警告我
She must have left this as a warning!
恶婆娘
Devious.
好了 这下上面也有我的指纹了
Dang it, I got my fingerprints all over it now.
我敢打包票车胎也是她扎坏的
I bet she was the one who gave me that flat tire.
给谁打电话呢
Who are you calling?
谁啊
Who was that?
她要付出代价了
She's going to pay.
你都不确定到底是不是她
You don't even know it was her.
不管怎么样 你先叫那人住手
Whatever that was, you got to call it off.
肯定是她 她眼神看着就不对劲
I know it was her. I saw the evil in her eyes.
万一人家有白内障呢
She probably has cataracts.
好吧 歌洛莉亚 是我干的
Oh, for God's sake, Gloria, I did it.
人形板是我偷的
I stole the cutout.
是你
You?
看那些男的在那猥琐地合影我就不爽
I didn't love the way those guys were taking pictures with it.
杰 但你从来不会这样吃醋的啊
Jay, but you've never been jealous like this.
一开始看到是不会吃醋
Well, when we first met,
但他们天天把你的牌子放在那
but then I realized it's a full-time job.
是我不好
I'm sorry.
想保护自己的老婆有什么不好的呢
There's nothing wrong with being protective of your wife.
这意味着你在乎我啊
It means that you care.
这会儿不会有人去对那老太太做什么吧
Is something bad happening to that poor woman?
细节我也不知道 我都交给他们去办了
I don't know details. I let them decide.
他们那帮人不喜欢被指手画脚
They don't like to feel managed.
求求你赶紧叫他们停手吧
I'm begging you to make that call!
爱丽丝姑姑还来过我们高中做过讲座呢
Auntie Alice spoke at Career Day at my high school!
你好
Hello?
没 我们没订花啊
No, we didn't order flowers.
就是他们 就说不要郁金香
That's them. Tell them no tulips.
不要郁金香
Uh, no tulips.
他们挂了
They hung up.
还好老娘记得这些黑话
Good thing that I remembered the code.
好了 我的老醋坛子
Okay, now, my big jealous man,
咱们喝点酒去吧
let's go and have some wine.
我也不知道为什么会对人形板耿耿于怀
I don't know why that cutout bugged me so much.
也许退休后我太闲了才有空吃醋
I guess probably because I have more time now to be jealous.
好了好了 你闲的话就把我带上楼去
Okay, now, you have more time to take me upstairs
给我演示下
and show me what those
那些臭男人都在商店对我做了什么吧
bad men were doing to me at the store.
我又重新爱上退休生活了
I'm getting back to liking retirement.
我是让你说的不要玫瑰 对吧
I told you to say no roses, right?
你说郁金香
Tulips!
应该差不多啦
I'm sure it's fine.
这是你要的威士忌
Here's the scotch you asked for.
我还有些话想跟你说
And also, there's something else.
我要把滑板车退回去了
I'm returning the hoverboard.
好吧 发票应该在盒子里
Fine. I-I think the receipt was in the box.
好的 行
Okay. Well, good.
因为我希望得到的尊重和肯定
Because I can't accept a gift if it's just a shiny
不是这种高级玩具能替代的
servo-controlled substitute for respect and appreciation.
看看我吧 克莱尔
I'm not invisible, Claire.
你老公是一位强壮能干的
You married a strong and capable man who --
你能帮我把链子解开吗
Can you help me with this clasp?
克莱尔
Claire?
亲爱的
Honey?
别 别哭啊
No. Don't cry.
你非要我留着也不是不可以啊
I-I can, uh -- I can keep it if you want.
反正也没法退 都有磨损了
I-I can't return it anyway. I already dented it.
不 不是这事
No, it's not that. It's -- it's not.
是工作的事 我压力好大
It's just all of this. I'm so stressed.
菲尔 我从没当过老板
Phil, I've never been a boss before,
我都要疯了
and I am freaking out.
但目前为止你表现得很棒啊
But you've been handled it so well.
都是装出来的 我自己都不知道在做什么
I am faking it, Phil. I have no idea what I'm doing.
我只是在模仿我爸
I'm just copying my dad --
牛排啊 威士忌啊 还有雪茄
the steak, the scotch, the cigars.
你知道我的胃有多烧得慌吗
Do you have any idea how bad the heartburn is?
但你才刚上手啊 慢慢来
But you just got here. Give it a little time.
哪有时间慢慢来 我现在是老大
There is no time. I'm in charge now.
我每天都活在恐惧中
And I live every day in constant fear
生怕被人发现我自欺欺人
of everyone discovering that I'm a fraud.
我的天 我果真是个强势的白人男性
Oh, my God, I really am a powerful white male!
听着 你没有自欺欺人
Hey, you are not a fraud.
我连坐上我爸椅子的
I haven't had the guts
胆儿都没有
to sit at my dad's desk since he left.
我依然觉得自己只是当年
I still feel like the little girl
那个在桌子底下玩躲猫猫的小姑娘
who used to play hide-and-seek under it.
听着
Look.
现在这是你的桌子了
This is your desk now.
是你应得的
You've earned it.
你不是当年那个小姑娘了
You are not a little girl anymore.
事实上 你是我认识的
In fact, you're the strongest,
最强大最聪明的女人
smartest woman I know.
维持咱们一大家子生活起居是最难的事业
The hardest company in the world to run is Dunphy Co.,
你都能坚持22年
and you've kept us in business for 22 years.
我一点也不担心你工作受阻
I don't worry about you in this job.
我还担心那些笨蛋追赶你的步伐太辛苦呢
I worry about the poor chump who has to follow you.
克莱尔 人都到齐可以开会了
Everyone is here for your meeting, Claire.
给他们点颜色吧 老大
Knock 'em dead, boss.
菲尔 等等
Uh, Phil, wait.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
多谢
Thank you...
你做的一切
for everything.
真心感谢
Thank you.
很抱歉我很少跟你言谢
And I'm sorry if I don't say it more.
抱抱
Come here.
我猜你又要去会议上挥斥方遒了
I guess you want to get rolling on your meeting.
我就先走了
I'll just duck out.
-滑板留着吧 -谢谢
-Take it. -Thank you.
克莱尔
Claire?
我爱你
I love you.
好了 玛格丽特
Okay, Margaret.
别动别动 让我转吧
No, no, no, no, no, let me spin!
你会帮倒忙的
It's worse if you try to help.
叫他们进来吧
Send them in.
菲尔
Phil?
不是吧 又来
Oh, no, not again.
要把他叫醒吗
Should we wake him up?
我看注意事项了
Oh, I read the instructions.
说最好不要
It says not to.
你好
Hello.
什么
What?
别担心 我是房屋中介
Don't worry. I'm a realtor.
我马上就到
I'll be right there.
我明天要早起开会
I have a really early meeting.
我去吧
I'm on it.
谢谢
Thank you.